Seidenberg, Jacob Additional Arbitration Files 5571
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files
1963-1975
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seidenberg, Jacob
5571
5 cubic feet
5 linear ft.
Arbitration decisions, reports, transcripts, papers.
5666404
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 11, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 13, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arbitration, Industrial; Seidenberg, Jacob
5666404
- Public Law Board No. 757 Power Terminal United Transportation Union, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Arbitration of Local Union 557 and B&P Motor Express, Inc. Before Jacob Seidenberg, Esquire, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- AAA Case No. 16 30 0062 72, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Scope and Contents
  B&P Motor Express and Local 557; December 18 1972
- Public Law Board No. 536, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  United Transportation Union v Aliquippa and Southern Railroad Company
- Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Local 272, FMCS File 72A/10370
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters and Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  AAA 1430023072 M-P
- Transcript of Proceedings, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  State of Maryland; October 17 1972; Case # 36387
- Bowon Transportation Co. District 50, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  FMCS 72A/9764
- Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania and Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  AAA 14300085 P- M
- Special Board of Adjustment No. 589, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Pennsylvania Railroad v BRT
- Arbitration- Printing Industry of Washington, DC, 1959-1962 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Local Lodge 175 of District Lodge 98, International Association of Mechanics and Aerospace Workers and AMF, Inc., 1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  November 4 1971
- Wage Hour 1971 Puerto Rico (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Mail Express and Warehouse Employees Local Union No. 730, IBT, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  FMCS 73 K 05718; February 1 1973
- Baltimore-Washington Newspaper Guild and AFL-CIO, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  AAA 1630001172; December 21 1972
- Arbitration, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local Union No. 924 and Bowaters Carolina Corporation; FMCS 72A/8815; June 6 1972
- National Airlines - National Airline Pilots System Board of Adjustment, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  July 10-11 1972
- Martinsville Nylon Employees Council Corp du Pont de Nemours and Co., 1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  AAA 1630 0019 70
- Asbestos Workers Local Union #23 and Philadelphia Asbestos Corporation, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Contains photographs; AAA 1430007071K
- Food Fair Stores and IBT, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  December 20, 27 1973; 74K03146
- Local No. 639 Drivers Chauffeurs and Helpers, IBT and Pep Lines Trucking Co., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  FMCS 72A/10628 July 31 1972
- Brunswick Pulp and Paper and International Brotherhood of Pulp Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 400, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  FMCS 72A/10253; July 14 1972
- Public Law Board No. 1217 and LI-BRAC, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Prince William County Education Association and Board of Education of Prince William County, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  AAA 1639013473
- McLean Trucking Local 557 and IBT, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  FMCS 74 K 04452; December 8 1973
- Teachers Association of Anne Arundel County, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Ann Arundel Board of Education - Teacher's Association of Anne Arundel County, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  July 27 1972; AAA 1630003972
- Public Law Boar No. 687, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  United Transportation Union - Akron, Canton and Youngstown Railroad Company; October 23 1970
- United Parcel Service - Local 639, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  FMCS 73 K012074; December 14 1973; January 12 1974
- International Union of Gas Workers - Washington Gas Light Company, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  FMCS 73 K04284; June 8 1973
- Public Law Board No. 1246 Western Pacific - BRAC, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Award No. 16 Public Law Board No. 468 - New Haven - BLE, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Award No. 14 Public Law Board 468, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Award No. 13 Public Law Board No. 468, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Award No. 12 Public Law Board No. 468, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Award No. 11 Public Law Board No. 468, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Award No. 8 Public Law Board No. 468, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Award No. 9 Public Law Board No. 468, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Award No. 10 Public Law Board No. 468, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Award No/ 7 Public Law Board No. 468, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Award No. 1 Public Law Board No. 468, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Award No. 2 Public Law Board No. 468, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Award No. 3 Public Law Board No. 468, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Award No. 4 Public Law Board No. 468, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Award No. 5 Public Law Board No. 468, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Award No. 6 Public Law Board No. 468, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Arbitration Board 338, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  May 13 1971; Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers; National Railway Labor Conference; Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committees
- The Kroger Company and Retail Wholesale and Department Store Union, AFL-CIO, Local 390, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  April 14, 21 1972
- Public Law Board No. 498, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Central of Georgia Railway Company; United Transportation Union (S)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local Union No. 1737 and Prince William Electric Cooperative, Inc., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  June 9 1972; FMCS 72A/8748
- Arbitration, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  Local 3-495 Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, AFL-CIO - Hercules, Incorporated; June 29, July 20 1972
- Public law Board No. 660, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers; Pittsburgh, Chartiers and Youghiogheny Railway Co.
- NAL-ALPA Case 100-70, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- national Airlines - ALPA, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  Case Number 66-70
- Public Law Board No. 669, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  United Transportation Union E; Penn Central Transportation Co. (Michigan Central Railroad)
- Arbitration, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Local Union No. 508; Westvaco, Charleston SC Plant; August 31 1972; FMCS 72A/9238
- District 50, Local 14084, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  Cohart Refractories Company; FMCS 72A/9242; July 17 1972
- Local No. 175 International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  FMCS 72A/7441
- Carpenter Local 340 - Prowler Industries, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  FMCS 72A/11268
- Public Law Board No 1109, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  Lehigh Valley Railroad Company; Brotherhood of Railroad, Airline and Steamship Clerks
- Public Law Board No. 656, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Wage and Hour Virgin Islands, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  January 1974
- United Transportation Union and Erie Lackawanna Railway Company, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Time Lost
- Award No. 1 Public Law Board No. 242, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Award No. 2 Public Law Board No. 242, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Award No. 9 Public Law Board No. 242, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Award No. 3-8 Public Law Board No. 242, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Award No. 11-12 Public Law Board No. 242, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- United Transportation Union (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Assorted Papers
- Public Law Board No. 1347 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  United Transportation Union; Assorted Papers
- Public Law Board No. 852, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Long Island Railroad; Brotherhood Railway Carmen
- Submission-Special Board No. 1514, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  United Transportation Union; Trainmen's Committee
- Virginia Electric and Power Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  FMCS 70A/9141; February 8, September 24, December 6 1971
- Docket 2143 ARSA v C&NW (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Docket No. 2165, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  November 4 1966
- Docket No. 2172, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  November 1 1966
- Docket No. 2171, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Fourth Division Docket No. 2152, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  September 7 1966
- Fourth Division Docket No. 9151, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Fourth Division Docket No. 9150, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Fourth Division Docket No. 2148, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  September 8 1966
- Fourth Division Docket No. 2149, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Fourth Division Docket No. 2146, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Fourth Division Docket No. 2147, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Fourth Division Docket No. 2145 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Fourth Division Docket No. 9144, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  September 9 1966
- Fourth Division Docket No. 2141, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Fourth Division Docket 9138, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Fourth Division Docket No. 9137, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Fourth Division Docket No. 2134, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Fourth Division Docket No. 2132, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Fourth Division Docket No. 2131, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Fourth Division Docket No. 2129, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Fourth Division Docket 2130, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Docket No. 2153, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Docket No. 2156, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Docket No. 2158, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Docket No. 2160, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Docket No. 2162, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  January 19 1967
- Docket No. 2164, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  November 2 1966
- Docket No. 2166, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Docket No. 2167, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Docket No. 2168, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Docket No. 2170, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  November 3 1966
- Docket No. 2173, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Docket No. 2174, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Docket No. 2175, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  January 18 1967
- Docket No. 2176, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Docket No. 2177, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Docket No 2180, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  January 16 1967
- Docket No. 2181, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Docket No. 2182-3-4, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Docket No. 2185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  January 17 1967
- Docket 2186, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  January 19 1967; October 31 1966
- Docket No. 2192, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Docket 2193, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Docket 2194, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Docket 2213, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  May 17 1967
- Docket No. 2215, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  May 16 1967
- Docket 2216, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Docket No. 2219, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Docket 2217, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Docket 2218, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Docket No. 2225, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Docket No. 2233, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Docket No. 2234, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Arbitration, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  Bakery and Confectionary Workers International Union of America, Local No. 358, AFL-CIO and The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company; FMCS 72A/6841
- Submission Public Law Board 1024, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers v The Western Pacific Railroad Company
- Public Board No. 772, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  PATH-BLE
- Airline Pilots Association and Eastern Airlines, Inc., 1972 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  EAL# 41-70; ALPA# 106-70
- Air Line Pilots Association and Eastern Air Lines, Inc., 1972 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  EAL# 54-71; ALP# 143-71
- Public Law Board No. 747, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  Brotherhood of Railway Signalmen; Reading Company
- Industry and Labor Relations Conference Israel, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  1/9-14/1972
- Arbitration Board 321A, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  National Railway Labor Conference; Railroad Yardmasters of America; September 22 1972
- Arbitration, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Printing Industry of Washington, Inc. Union Employers Division and Bookbinders and Bindery Workers Union No. 144
- BLE and CMSTP&P-East, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Docket No. 39836; November 7 1963
- Atlanta Printing Specialties Local 527 Mead Packaging Company, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  FMCS 71A/10357
- Mead Papers and International Union of District 50 - ATW, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  FMCS 72A/2767
- Special Board of Adjustment, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  PRR v BRT
- Crown Cork and Seal Company and International Association of Machinists, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  FMCS 73K/4310
- Public Law Board No. 326 Award No. 44, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and Penn Central Transportation Company
- Arbitration, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  District Lodge No. 67, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO and Thompson's Dairy, Inc.; FMCS 72A/435
- United Steelworkers of America and KD Manufacturing Company, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  AAA 1430053971J
- Arbitration, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians, Local 31 and National Broadcasting Company; AAA 1630005472
- Public Board No. 916, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Brotherhood Railway Carmen and Long Island Railroad
- Bakery and Confectionary Workers Local 68 and Schmidt Baking Co., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  FMCS 72A/7912
- Public Law Board No/ 442, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  United Transportation Union and The Cuyahoga Valley Railway Company
- Public Law Board No. 535, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Rock Island; United Transportation Union
- Carroll County Education Association and the Carroll County Board o education, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  AAA 16001272
- First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  June 1972 - December 1972
- Special Board of Adjustment No. 258, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and the Reading Company; Case No. 3749 E-1284 E-68 P-17 6/68
- Public Law Board No. 1347, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  United Transportation Union (T); Erie Lackawanna Railway Company
- Western Warehousing Company (PC) and Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  Public Law Board No. 880